我知道我们公司不那么传统 不同于他人
I know we're a little unorthodox,we're a little
做事情有点高调
loud in the way we do things. But you gotta understand,
不过你们要理解
we're the new guys on the block,you know,
我们属于新人 这是在打响名声
we're trying to make a name for ourselves.
但你们必须知道的是 我们不做
But I want you to understand,we don't
任何违法的事
do anything illegal.
无论如何都不会
Whatsoever.
你可以去找证监会
I mean,you could talk to the SEC.
他们过去半年内来我们公司有15次了吧
They were at my office 15 times over the last six months.
我没有什么好隐瞒的
I mean,I got... I got nothing to hide.
你也知道证监会属于民间监管组织
Well,you know the SEC is a civil regulatory agency.
我们查的是刑事犯罪
We pursue criminal activities.
没错 你们抓的是真正的罪犯啊
Exactly! You go after real criminals,which